{
    "subject": "resource/Joyalukkas",
    "predicate": "ontology/regionServed",
    "object": "resource/Singapore",
    "human_readable": "Joyalukkas serves Singapore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837409257888794,
            "question": "Does Joyalukkas provide services in Singapore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9402347207069397,
            "question": "Is Joyalukkas a business located in Singapore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9386792182922363,
            "question": "Is Joyalukkas a business based in Singapore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9090576171875,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Joyalukkas and Singapore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8729656338691711,
            "question": "Does Joyalukkas operate internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7625275254249573,
            "question": "Where does Joyalukkas operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6860045194625854,
            "question": "What does 'serves' mean in this context regarding Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5732581615447998,
            "question": "Where can you find Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5723757743835449,
            "question": "Which country is associated with Joyalukkas' operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49000057578086853,
            "question": "What kind of establishment is Joyalukkas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joyalukkas serves Singapore.",
            "html": "dbpedia_872_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country is associated with Joyalukkas' operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_872_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_872_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'serves' mean in this context regarding Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_872_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_872_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Joyalukkas has showrooms and operates in Singapore.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"Joyalukkas serves Singapore.\" The documents mention Joyalukkas' presence and activities in Singapore, including its showrooms, customer base, and charitable contributions."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Joyalukkas operates in and serves the Singapore market. These include details about its showrooms, local presence, and various promotional activities in Singapore."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}